you
[Music]
so this is a very quick housekeeping
film with four announcements the first
is we've got some really great content
coming up we've just done really good
interview with Gabor Mattei which is
gonna be part of a whole series that
we're going to bring out on psychedelics
the second is that we're about to do a
Q&A and we're gonna give the other
details in a second of how to kind of
contribute questions to that third we've
got some really interesting stuff coming
up on patreon and fourth is the launch
of rebel wizard live which is our live
streamed event series starting with one
we're quite excited about which is
called the war on art with Tim lot who
regular viewers will be familiar with
and the author Lionel Shriver who wrote
We Need to Talk About Kevin and they're
going to be talking about censorship and
political correctness in literature and
art
so it's been a while since we've done a
QA and the thing that we're trying to
juggle like the complicating factor is
that we want to give priority to patrons
if you're supporting us on patreon then
if you're supporting us ten dollars or
more then you'll guaranteed an answer to
your question five dollars one dollar
you would be more likely to answer that
but then we've got the issue that we the
the tags that people have on YouTube
don't necessarily match with the the
patron that their real names on patreon
so what we're going to do if you're if
you're a patron send your question on
email to this address that's coming
on-screen now and also but if you're not
a patron put a question in underneath
the line here we'll we'll answer
whatever we get round to but will
guarantee to answer $10 and up if you're
a five-dollar patron you're probably
going to get your question answered one
dollar will we'll consider it more but
we'll also look through the questions
underneath this and if there's one who
particularly liked them we'll definitely
answer those and talking of patreon
we're also going to be launching some
exclusive content on there very soon the
first one is the story of rebel wisdom
so it's the two of us kind of giving a
little bit more background into what
we're doing what our mission is how this
all came about yeah so that will be
coming up very soon so increasingly
we'll be putting stuff on to patreon
either as early access or as exclusive
content because this is now a full-time
job so the way that we at the moment are
thinking that we're going to make it
sustainable is by upping the amount of
stuff on patreon and encouraging people
to subscribe so if you like that content
if you like while putting out there then
please do subscribe on patreon we
there's some really good stuff up there
already for example Tim lot talking
about the similarities and differences
between Jordan Peterson and Alan Watts
we have the second half of our really
amazing interview with Warren Farrell
and also the second half of our
interview with Douglas Murray and a lot
of other really good content as well so
please do sign up on patreon ask us a
question below the line and yeah see you
see